ASHWIN SINGH

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT

- **4** 647-823-8722
- 🖂 Ashwin.Singh.087@gmail.com
- AshwinSingh.dev
- in /in/AshwinSingh087
- /Ashwin087

PROFILE

I am Front-End Developer with a passion for building accessible apps with a good UI. My experience in government and planning allows me to take ideas and bring them to life; managing projects and solving problems to meet deadlines is in my DNA. I love working collaboratively with others and always bring good vibes to the team.

EDUCATION

JUNO COLLEGE Oct 2020 - July 2021

- Web Development Bootcamp
- Web Development & JavaScript

YORK UNIVERSITY Sept 2011 - June 2015

• Kinesiology and Health Science

SKILLS









Firebase







React



Rest APIs

PROJECTS

NOTBLOCKBUSTER 🗹 😱



React | Firebase | Rest API | CSS 3 | Mob Programmed Movie app that allows users to explore and save movies to a filterable list connected to Firebase.

DAILY CRYPTO UPDATE 🗹 🞧



ES6 JavaScript | SASS | Rest API | Pair Programmed Searchable cryptocurrency app with an accessible autosuggest search bar users can select from.

ARTIST DISCOGRAPHY 🗹 🞧



React | Firebase | Rest API | HTML 5 | CSS 3 Music app that allows users to find an artist's discography and save their favorite albums to a list stored on Firebase.

EXPERIENCE

WORK MATERIAL PLANNER

Bombardier Aerospace | Feb 2019 - June 2020

- Worked cross-functionally with other departments including engineering and production to resolve issues and ensure deliverables were completed on time.
- Utilized SAP and Bombardier specific software to manage inventory and proactively procure required materials to assure production deadlines were met.
- Managed logistic inquiries by addressing and resolving issues that occurred, advising other departments about proper procedures and correct next steps, and expediting urgent deliverables.

JUNIOR POLICY ANALYST

Ontario Public Service | Sept 2017 - Dec 2017

- Led the development of a joint ministry pilot project which included determining the approach, structuring the program, drafting all necessary documents, and facilitating the approval process with senior management.
- Liaised with other divisions and ministry partners to coordinate program development and implementation, provide opportunities for engagement and updates about recent developments on key files.